taxslayerpro.com 2004-04-01

# TaxSlayer® Pro

**YOUR PRIVACY IS A PRIORITY TO US**

At TaxSlayerPro.com(TaxSlayer®), we are committed to safeguarding customer information. Since your privacy is a priority to us, TaxSlayer will not share nonpublic information about you with third parties outside of the TaxSlayer corporate family without your consent, except as explained in our Privacy Policy.

We have created our Privacy Policy to communicate our privacy commitment to you, and to serve your privacy needs.

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Protecting your privacy is important to TaxSlayer. We want you to understand what information we may gather and how we may share it. This Privacy Policy explains TaxSlayer's collection, use, retention and security of information about you.

How We Collect Information   

Visiting our Web Site   
We will not collect personal information about you just because you visit this site. In order to improve the usefulness of our web site for our visitors, we automatically collect and maintain statistical information from our site's data logs that concern network traffic flow and volume. This information consists of:  
The name of the domain from which the visitor accesses the Internet (e.g., "a company.com"; "a school.edu"; or "an agency.gov");  
The Internet Protocol Number; and  
The date and time the IRS web site is visited.

This information does not identify individual visitors and is used to enhance and improve your experience on our site. No attempts are made to identify individual users unless illegal behavior is suspected.

Purchasing our Products   
The purpose of this site is to market and sell our software. As a result, you may have to provide us your personal information and/or email address. We do not share or disseminate this information to other vendors or clients.  This information is kept in strictest, secure, confidence. If you choose to purchase our products online, you will be asked for personal information as well as your credit card number.  The forms requesting this information are on a secure server.  All steps are taken to safeguard your information.

Sharing Information  
Within TaxSlayer Corporate Family   
We may share information about you and the products and services you have purchased from us, among members of the TaxSlayer Corporate family, all of whom follow our Privacy Policy. However, this information will not be provided to third parties outside or corporate family, except as noted below: 

With Service Providers   
In some cases, we employ service providers to provide a product you order, to fulfill a service you request, or to market one of our products or services. Examples include delivering downloadable products, offering online software applications, or sending e-mails on our behalf. While this may require us to share information, these service providers are strictly prohibited from using your information other than to act on our behalf.

For Legal Reasons   
We may be required to provide information about you to third parties outside of the TaxSlayer corporate family without your consent as provided by law, such as, to respond to a subpoena or court order, judicial process or regulatory authorities, to protect against fraud.

In Case of Sale of Company   
Your information may be transferred in connection with a proposed or actual sale, merger, or transfer of all or a portion of a business or operating unit.

Our Former Customers   
Even if you are no longer a TaxSlayer customer, our Privacy Policy will continue to apply to you.

Our Security Practices and Information Accuracy   
We take every step available to safeguard customer information. All forms accepting user information are processed on our secure servers.

TaxSlayer's electronic filing process is different than most in the fact that you download our software and install it on your personal PC. Once you have completed the return on your personal PC, you are asked to transmit the return to TaxSlayer's secure website. The tax return file is encrypted to avoid any unwanted detection. Immediately after the files are transmitted to TaxSlayer's website, they are moved to a different location providing less likelihood of unwanted intervention. They are again moved a third time to begin processing. All acknowledgements are handled by e-mail with only general information given. Acknowledgements can also be retrieved via our website again without general information provided. (Example: IRS accepted or rejected, acceptance date, etc.) Confidential information such as refund amounts, names, addresses, and account numbers are not displayed or e-mailed.

We strive to keep our customer information as accurate and complete as we can. If you believe any of the information about you is not accurate, please let us know.

Other Information   
The Privacy Policy applies to products and services of TaxSlayer®. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy, and any of the policies described above, at any time. The examples contained within this Privacy Policy are illustrations; they are not intended to be exclusive.

* * *
